{
    "subject": "resource/P._Harrison",
    "predicate": "ontology/party",
    "object": "resource/United_National_Party",
    "human_readable": "P. Harrison was a member of the United National Party.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8989506363868713,
            "question": "What political party was P. Harrison a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8616308569908142,
            "question": "What was the name of the party P. Harrison belonged to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7982404232025146,
            "question": "Which political party did P. Harrison represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7938479781150818,
            "question": "What political party was P. Harrison associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.793066680431366,
            "question": "Was P. Harrison affiliated with any political parties?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7758020758628845,
            "question": "To which organization did P. Harrison belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7550719976425171,
            "question": "P. Harrison's political affiliation was with which group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5626946687698364,
            "question": "P. Harrison's political leanings were towards which group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5480131506919861,
            "question": "In what political context was P. Harrison involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5105715394020081,
            "question": "Was P. Harrison involved in any political movements?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=P. Harrison was a member of the United National Party.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4875_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what political context was P. Harrison involved?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4875_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=P. Harrison's political leanings were towards which group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4875_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=P. Harrison's political affiliation was with which group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4875_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4875_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the provided context information documents mention that P. Harrison was indeed a member of the United National Party (UNP) in Sri Lanka, with one document explicitly stating his membership (\"He was a member of the United National Party (UNP)\") and another mentioning his role as a Member of Parliament for several decades within the UNP."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Harrison was a member of the United National Party (UNP)\", which directly supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}